bloggersbase.com 2009-06-14

# Privacy Policy

**_BLOGGERSBASE – PRIVACY POLICY_**

BloggersBase respects your right to privacy. Please read below to understand more about our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy applies to the BloggersBase website (" **Website** ") and governs data collection and usage therein and in connection thereto. By using our Website, accessing, browsing, using the Content or otherwise submitting information to the Website, you acknowledge and consent to the collection and use of information by BloggersBase, as set forth below and in the Terms of Use, as posted in the Website ( **"ToU"** ). 

**All terms in capital letters not otherwise defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the BloggersBase ToU. This Privacy Policy is hereby attached by reference to the ToU, and serves as an integral part thereof. For clarification purposes, Sections 1 of the ToU shall apply to this privacy policy, _mutatis mutandis._**

**Collection of your Personal Information**

BloggersBase collects some or all of your personal and/or identification information, such as your e-mail address and/or your name. BloggersBase also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites ** _._**

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by BloggersBase. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website addresses. 

The information as described above is used by BloggersBase for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and for general statistics regarding use of the Website and use habits of the Website's users.

Without derogating from the foregoing, please keep in mind that if the Content that you upload to the Website includes any personal and/or identification information or other personally sensitive data, such information is in the public domain, and may be collected and used by others. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

BloggersBase collects and uses your personal information for registration purposes, and also for statistical purposes as set forth above. BloggersBase may also use such information for promotion purposes, such as to offer to you certain products or services of BloggersBase or others. BloggersBase may also contact you via surveys for examination of current or potential services and/or functionalities of the Website.

BloggersBase does not sell, rent or leases its users lists to third parties. BloggersBase may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) shall not be transferred to such third parties. In addition, BloggersBase may share such unique personally identifiable information with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to BloggersBase, and they are or shall be (as the case may be) required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

BloggersBase does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

BloggersBase keeps track of the Website in general, and of our users' visits of the Website in particular, in order to determine popularity of certain features, functionality of the Website and for other purposes, including commercial purposes. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the Website to users whose behavior indicates that they are more interested in a particular subject area.

BloggersBase will disclose your personal information as provided in the Website to third parties, without notice, only if: (a) BloggersBase is required to do so by law, or if (b) BloggersBase believes in good faith that such action is necessary to conform or comply with the provisions of any law or with legal proceedings, to protect the rights or property of BloggersBase and/or to protect the personal safety of users of BloggersBase or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize BloggersBase pages, or register with BloggersBase site or services, a cookie helps BloggersBase to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as addresses, username and so on. When you return to the Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the BloggersBase features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the BloggersBase services or web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

BloggersBase reasonably secures the personally identifiable information you provide from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, on computer servers in a controlled and secured environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

**Changes to this Policy**

BloggersBase may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, by placement of an updated policy in the Website. BloggersBase encourages you to periodically review this policy from time to time, so to be informed of the subject matters hereof.

**Contact Information**

BloggersBase welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that BloggersBase has not adhered to this policy, please contact BloggersBase at info@bloggersbase.com, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to attend your comment.

**Miscellaneous**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Israel, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Any claim or dispute between you and BloggersBase that arises in whole or in part from the Website and/or in connection with the use thereof, shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Tel Aviv – Jaffa, Israel. 

***
